



ORAGAN DIMITRIJEVIC CURRICULUM VITAE

Table of Contents

Curriculum Vitae

About	2
Education	4
Work Experinces	5
Projects	9
Skills	13

About

Personal Information



Dragan Dimitrijevic

☑ dragan@tenfoldpath.com

**** +45 26355730

™ Serbian

Danish

30.11.1978

Introduction

With the 15 years of experience in the industry, I would like to help companies develop modern and scalable cloud solutions.

I have 4 years experience developing software in AWS, working primarily with services such as ECS, EC2, Lambda, API Gateway, CloudFront, VPC and S3. I enjoy working on cloud based solutions as they offer scalability and a wide variety of services which can be used to build feature rich applications.

I have a great deal of interest in working with Open Source technologies. Integrations and application development are the areas in which I spent most of my professional time. My most recent technology stack is NodeJs and Javascript together with Typescript and Angular. In my spare time I enjoy training, running and spending time with my friends and family.

Languages

- Serbian (native)
- English

Danish

Education

Information and Communication Technology

Engineering College of Copenhagen

2003 - 2006

DU3 Modul 5, Prøve i Dansk 3

K.I.S.S

2004 - 2005

Datamatician (Information Technology)

Niels Brock

2001 - 2003

Work Experiences

Software Architect - Head of product

Nordlid

Jan 2018 - Nov 2019

Since many of the Norlid's clients use Eloqua as a marketing automation platform, I wask working on developing custom solutions and integrations. Most of the solutions whould typicaly involve a specific business logic added on top of Eloqua, which would handle Contacts, Email Content or manage Assets in campaign canvas. Integrations where concerning primarily with importing Contacts and related data from different sources, and exporting data on Contact activities such as email clicks, web visits, push response etc.

As a result of many years of developing software arround Eloqua, a series of products have emerged as standard packages. These SaaS type solutions where designed to be installed across instances and serve the needs of multiple clients. With my second role as a 'Head of product', I had a responsibility to create standard software based on the experiences from custom solutions. All the applications have been developed and hosted on AWS cloud.

Besides building software for Eloqua, I had an opportunity to develop a backend and mobile application for "Få tiden tilbage" project which took six months to complete.

CTO

Globase International

Jul 2016 - Dec 2017

My second time at Globase, although very different role in terms of responsibities and a new company owner (Mailup Group). Like with the most company acquisitions, the change of ownerwhip and culture can have a strong impact on orgamisations. Appart from the structural and strategical changes, the company had to go through a discovery process in terms of technology and infrastructure.

One of the biggest and most challenging projects during my time at Globase was the migration of hardware. We needed to change location withing the same hosting provider but which powered all the services neccessary for the operation of the from one hosting location to another at QSC. This meant that most of the underlying services which powered platforms had to be restarted and reconfigured, from database servers, load balancers, web servers.

List of responsibilities

- Managing development team (Agile SCRUM)
- Maintaining in house platforms and custom solutions
- Pre-sales and requirement specification
- Maintaining hardware in QSC
- Management group

Another big undertaking was the migrattion of the V2 platform from QSC to a new cloud setup at Mailup hosting center in Cremona. Even though we could not complete the migration due to the high level of complexity and unforeseeable issues, we were able to implement continuous deployment on the existing setup, since the V2 platform was fully virtualized in a development environment.

System Developer

Increase

Nov 2015 - Jun 2016

Most of my time at Increase I spent working with Oracles's marketing automation platform Eloqua. I was building apps and data integrations in the AWS cloud. One of the more interesting project during that time, was the development of the Event App. This application was designed to handle the event flow by creating many assets (Email, Landing Page, Registration Form,

Custom Data Object etc) on a campaign canvas in Eloqua, which can handle the invitation, registration and keep track of the participation status.

System Developer

Globase

Apr 2014 - Oct 2015

Similar to my previous job, at Globase I was developing solutions and integrations against yet another email marketing automation platform. This involved a variaty of tasks such as integrating external data sources for email content, implementing contest strategies such as polls, quiz and giveaways.

Software Developer

Brandhouse

Mar 2013 - Mar 2014

At Brandhouse, I had a chance of working on a platform (Publicator) made for graphic design and print. The tasks where including integration with data sources, implementing new feature requests and collecting requirement specification from a customer.

Developer

Peytz & Co

Sep 2011 - Feb 2013

This was my first job in the Marketing industry where I had an opportunity to work with an email automation platoform. I developed new features and custom solutions which would allow users to integrate content from external sources such as SOAP API, REST API, XML Feeds etc.

Developer

MOCH

Mar 2007 - Aug 2011

During my time a MOCH, I worked on a modular SCORM compliant LMS (Learning Management System) platform. My tasks were development of modules (LMS Courses, Workflow, Questionnaire), adding features and fixing issues.

Developer

Tang Data A/S

Jul 2006 - Feb 2007

My first work experience was developing on an inhouse ERP platform designed for veterinarians. I worked primarily on migrating from an old version, adding new features and troubleshooting reported problems.

Projects

Airship

This integration project was about making Eloqua send push messages using multi channel messaging platform Airship. The integration was covering following use cases:

- Send push message from campaign canvas (including scheduled and in-app)
- Send push message from a segment (batch)
- Send push message on form post
- · Import devices to Eloqua
- Collect activity response

Techstack



Få tiden tilbage

"Få tiden tilbage" was an interesting projects that took almost 6 month to complete. The client was a public transpaoration copmany (DSB) and the concept was focusing on bringing back value to the passangeres who experince dealays, due to the maintenance work done on the railways. The first release of the application was dealing with the journeys, where a passenger was to able to check in on the begining of the journey, and checkout on the destination, earning a certain amount of minutes. Every journey route had a defined award, and every journey was adding to the total of the time saved.

The second release of the application was dealing with the in-app ticket purchase based on the time (points) saved.

You can read more about this project for which Norlid won the Danish Digital Award in the category "Digital Activation"

Techstack



Rich Relevance

Thias project was an Eloqua application using Rich Relevance Customer Experience and Personalization Platform. The content personalization was implemented using products Recommend and Engage. The main objective was to integrate personalized content into Email Templates by using 'Cloud Content' drag'n'drop feature in Eloqua. This would enable marketeer to configure a cloud service so that the content can by generated dynamicaly as email get opened.

There were two kinds of content types that could be integrated, related products and content promotion.

Recommend

Engage

Enagage was content in the sense of product advertizement, banner content etc.

Techstack



Event App

The main objective of this project was to create an application which would help fasciliate event management in Eloqua. In many cases managing events can be a repetative task, requiring

many hours of work in order to setup the necessary logic for an event flow. Tracking changes in participation status. and handling waiting list for This application atteps to do exactly that, save the marketeer from manual work and create the pattern for the participation flow.

Event Assets

During the event creation process, many Eloqua assets are being created and integrated into the campagin canvas. Assets such as Segment, Email, Form, Landing Page, Custom Data Objects and Campagin are created and configured in order to support invitation, registration, unregistration and waiting list email notifications. When a Segment is ready and the campaign activated, the Contacts on that segment would recieve an inviation email and by clicking on the registration link, enter the flow.

Participation Flow

A participant can have different status changes such as registered, attended, unregistered and waiting. All these status changes can be initiated within the application and stored in the Custom Data Object in Eloqua.

Participation flow via Processing steps (registered, attended, waiting)

Asset Templates (pre defined templates for unified look and feel)

- Participation flow (invitation, registration, unregistration, waiting list)
- Aasset management such as registration forms, processing steps, landing pages, emails and custom data object connecting all assets in a campaign canvas.

Application can handle participant attendance, different flows (invitation, registration, unregistration) and waiting list for booked events.

Techstack



Skills

General Nodejs Linux Typescript Javascript PHP Ruby MySQL Apache Qt/C++ HTML5/CSS3 Git

Frameworks	
Express	
Angular	
Angular Material	
lonic	
Serverless	
TypeORM	
Sequelize	
Laravel	
Codeigniter	
Jekyll	

AWS	
EC2	
ECS	
Lambda	
API Gateway	
S3	
CloudFront	
CloudWatch	
Cloudivateri	
VPC	